JANUS QUEK

• DETAILS •

Singapore +65 8189 8717

janus.quek@gmail.com

Place of birth Singapore

Nationality Singaporean

• LINKS •

https://janusquek.tech/

https://linkedin.com/in/janus-quek/

• SKILLS •

C++

C#

Python

Unity

Unreal Engine

Microsoft Office

Adobe Photoshop

• LANGUAGES •

English

Chinese

Japanese

• HOBBIES •

Video Gaming Story Writing Music Composition

PROFILE

Experienced in C# Scripting Integration via Mono, adaptive audio technology via FMod, editor programming via IMGUI, serialization via Rapidjson, memory management, and gameplay programming via C# scripting.

Attained various academic achievements and project awards during my time in Digipen.

Currently on a scholarship with The Infocomm Media Development Authority of Singapore.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Game Design, DigiPen Institute of Technology Singapore, Singapore

September 2018 — December 2021

GPA: 3.71

Admitted into the Director's List every semester

Helped develop Howl: A Tale of Wolves in 2019:

3rd Place for Claude Comair Grand Prize for Game of the Year

Best Sophomore Game

Best Sophomore Technology

Finalist - Best 2D Graphics Technology

Finalist - Most Innovative Design

Helped develop Spellthief in 2018:

Best Freshman Technology

Finalist - Best 2D Physics Technology

Finalist - Best Music and Sound Design

Finalist - Best Artificial Intelligence

Game and Entertainment Technology, Temasek Polytechnic, Singapore

April 2013 — March 2016

Admitted into the Director's List for AY2013/2014 October semester

Contracted by the school after graduation to work on a game for research purposes

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

National Serviceman at National Service, Singapore

October 2016 — August 2018

Programmer Intern at Bandai Namco Studios Singapore, Singapore

October 2015 — March 2016

Worked on a prototype of a new game idea in Unreal Engine 4

Worked with both Blueprints and C++ on Unreal Engine 4

Worked with WPF in C# in developing a time-in time-out software

Worked with MySQL to create a database to work in conjunction with said software

REFERENCES

References available upon request